

# Krishnaveni L

27/09/1990 🏳 Indian 🔈 Burj Al Arab, Hamdan Street, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates □ 00971-582902264 ☑ lkrishnaveni27990@gmail.com (i) Husband Sponsorship



#### Profile

stack Web developer with 2years hands experience Mern on node Express, React, RestAPIs, GIThub, HTML5, PHP, C, C++, CSS, jQuery, javascript, .net, BOOTSTRAP-5, Nginx, AWS Cloud, Flutter . Also also proficient in designing, testing, web developing and developing Software to meet the needs of the customer according to the HLD and LLD. Have a good knowledge on MONGODB, SQL, Data Structures and Algorithms and CCNA certified.



### **Experience**

05/2022 - Present Abu Dhabi,

United ArabEmirates

04/2019 - 12/2019Kerala

04/2018 - 11/2018Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates

02/2016 - 08/2016 kottayam

11/2013 - 04/2015 Bengaluru, India

02/2012 - 06/2012Bihar, India

04/2011 - 08/2011 Thiruvananthapuram, India

## **Junior Web Developer**

#### One Avanue

Skills used: React node js, nodejs Express, Git Hub, Nginx, Flutter, Bootstrap, ccs, html, jquery, Mongo DB, Rest APIs

## Trainee-Php web developer

#### Data tech

Skills used: Php, Laravel, Word press, Json, Ajax, GIT, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

#### Trainee .NET web developer **Time Training Institute**

Skills used: C++,C#,.NET,ASP.NET,HTML,CSS,Git

#### Trainee developer **IPSR** solution

skills used:Java,Jscript,Jquery

## Software developer

#### Aricent

Skills used:C,C++,Java,RestAPIs,Git

## Trainee Engineer

#### BELTRON

Skills Used: voIP, Telecommunication, Networking

## **TraineeEngineer**

#### **BSNL**

Skills used: GSM, LTE, 4G, TDD, FDD

#### Education

06/2009 - 06/2013 Bihar, India

#### **Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering** Birla Institute Of Technology

GPA - 8

04/2007 - 04/2008Kerala, India

XII St. Theresa's Bethany Convent



GPA - 9.4

06/2005 - 04/2006 Kerala, India

**Mahatma Girls High School** GPA - 9.5



#### Skills

_	PRO	GRA	MMING	SKILLS

C ....

C++**Professional** 

HTML **Professional** 

SQL **Professional** 

**JAVA Professional**  node js, node js express **Professional** 

RestAPIs **Professional** 

GIT hub **Professional** 

HTML,CSS,BOOTSTRAP **Professional** 

**NGINX Professional** 

- COMPUTER AND IT SKILLS

User Interface / User Experience

Data Structures and Algorithms

iOS Programming Experience

....

....

0000

- LANGUAGES

2013

2011

English 00000 Malayalam 00000

Hindi 0000 Tamil Full

### **Awards**

**Best Project Technical Award** 2014 ARICENT

**Completed PRISM** 2014 **ARICENT** 

> **Excellent academic project of Electronics and Communication** department

Birla Institute of Technology

Secured 3rd position in Srijan of Technika Birla institute of technology



#### Certificates

**CCNA** Cisco

Cisco ID: CSCO12908178



enthusiastic team player

deep creative thinker

customer-focused

Action oriented

Assessing the needs of customers

Accuracy

self learner